(Penny:)Well, in that case,
do you mind giving me some advice?
(Leonard:)About Stuart?
(Leonard:)Love to.
(Penny:)He's very shy. How do I make him
feel more comfortable around me?
Well, first of all, don't underestimate
the value of discomfort.
- Really?
- Well, yeah. Stuart thrives under pressure.
(Leonard:)That's why he works
in a comic-book store.
[PHONE RINGING]
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Leonard:)It's Stuart.
[PHONE RINGING]
(Sheldon:)You're not going to answer it?
(Leonard:)He wants to talk about Penny.
I don't wanna talk about Penny.
(Sheldon:)You're making an assumption.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps the comic book store is on fire.
(Sheldon:)And he needs your assistance.
(Leonard:)Why would he call me?
(Sheldon:)We don't know.
(Sheldon:)And if you don't answer the phone,
we can't know.
(Leonard:)I'm not answering the phone, Sheldon.